Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/diepngtran96 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Interface Design Kotlin Transact-SQL (T-SQL)

Certifications

English for Business and Entrepreneurship MOOC

Get Started Querying with Transact-SQL

Diep Nguyen Tran

Technical Business Analyst

Ho Chi Minh City Metropolitan Area

Summary

I am a Business Analyst who was experienced Mobile Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Android, Microsoft Office, and Java. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information Technology from RMIT University.

Experience

Aurecon

Technical Business Analyst October 2022 - Present (2 years 6 months)

Live group
Technical Business Analyst
November 2021 - October 2022 (1 year)

ASIM Telecom Business Analyst January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Spring Knowledge Global Joint Stock Company Mobile Developer January 2018 - January 2021 (3 years 1 month)

Education

RMIT University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology (2015 - 2018)